University of Connecticut, Provost's Office Records 1989.0003
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series XI: Assistant Provost [Galvin Gall], 1968-1973
  - Dugan, David: Columbia University (Box 61:, Folder 2493)
  - Economics, Department of (Box 61:, Folder 2494-2496)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 61:, Folder 2497)
  - ETV Task Force (CHE) (Box 61:, Folder 2498)
  - Entrance Examination Board, College (Box 61:, Folder 2499)
  - Exchange Visitor Waiver Review Board ( George France) (Box 61:, Folder 2500)
  - Family Economics and Management, Dept. of (Box 61:, Folder 2501)
  - Faculty-Alumni Center (Box 61:, Folder 2502)
  - Fine Arts, School of (Box 61:, Folder 2503)
  - Grading Procedures: Spring Semester (Box 62:, Folder 2504)
  - Graduate School (Box 62:, Folder 2505)
  - G.S.R. Committee (Box 62:, Folder 2506)
  - Hartford T.T.T. Program (Box 62:, Folder 2507)
  - Health Services (Box 62:, Folder 2508-2511)
  - Health Service: Baskin (Box 62:, Folder 2512)
  - Health Service: Dr. Ransom (Box 62:, Folder 2513)
  - Higher Education Task Force on External Degrees and College Credit by Examination, Commission for (Box 62:, Folder 2514)
  - Higher Education Compact Feasibility Study (Box 62:, Folder 2515)
  - Higher Education for Urban Studies (HECUS) (Box 62:, Folder 2516-2518)
  - Honors Program Search Committee (Box 62:, Folder 2519)
  - Honors Program and State Universities, A Survey of (Box 62:, Folder 2520)
  - Independent Study 299: Course Survey (Box 62:, Folder 2521)
  - Information Services (Box 62:, Folder 2522)
  - International House (Box 62:, Folder 2523)
  - Italian Year Abroad (Box 62:, Folder 2524)
  - Joint Council on Economics Education, CT (Box 62:, Folder 2525)
  - Kellogg Foundation (Box 62:, Folder 2526)
  - New Careers Program (Box 63:, Folder 2527)
  - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, Inc. (Box 63:, Folder 2528)
  - New England Center for Continuing Education (Box 63:, Folder 2529)
  - Pharmacy, School of (Box 63:, Folder 2530)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 63:, Folder 2531)
  - Physical Education, School of (Box 63:, Folder 2532)
  - Physical Therapy, School of (Box 63:, Folder 2533)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, Meeting at (Box 63:, Folder 2534)
  - Psychiatrist, University: Search Committee (Box 63:, Folder 2535)
  - Radio and Television Center News (Box 63:, Folder 2536)
  - Registrar (Box 63:, Folder 2537-2538)
  - R.O.T.C. Study (Box 63:, Folder 2539)
  - Scholastic Standards, Committee on (Box 63:, Folder 2540)
  - Search Committee, University Psychiatrist (Box 63:, Folder 2541)
  - See, Harold W. (Dr.) (Box 63:, Folder 2542)
  - Semester on the Thirties (Box 63:, Folder 2543)
  - Senior Survey, 1970 (Box 63:, Folder 2544-2545)
  - Student Personnel, Division of (Box 63:, Folder 2546)
  - Subcommittee on Faculty Involvement in Planning New Programs (Box 63:, Folder 2547)
  - Summer Italian Program (Box 63:, Folder 2548)
  - Summer Sessions (Box 63:, Folder 2549)
  - Transfer Policies and Procedures (Box 63:, Folder 2550)
  - University of Connecticut Foundation (Box 63:, Folder 2551)
- Series XII: Associate Provost [William Orr], 1966-1979
  - Affirmative Action Committee, 1974 March - 1975 June (Box 64:, Folder 2552)
  - Chronology and Correspondence between UConn and HEW, 1972-1974 July (Box 64:, Folder 2553)
  - Complaints and Suggestions, 1973-1974 (Box 64:, Folder 2554)
  - Developing drafts in progress (Box 64:, Folder 2555)
  - Drafts published in Chronicle (Box 64:, Folder 2556)
  - HEW Affirmative Action Program, 1974- (Box 64:, Folder 2557)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1974 May 22 (Box 64:, Folder 2558)
  - Drafts (Box 64:, Folder 2559)
  - Memoranda, 1974 January - June (Box 64:, Folder 2560)
  - Press release, 1973 November 27 (Box 64:, Folder 2561)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1974 March 15 (Box 64:, Folder 2562)
  - HEW Report of Findings, 1972 November 2 (Box 64:, Folder 2563)
  - Miscellaneous input material, 1972-1974 (Box 64:, Folder 2564)
  - Other institutions' Affirmative Action Plans (Box 64:, Folder 2565-2567)
  - Preparation of departmental plans, 1974 June (Box 64:, Folder 2568)
  - Salary cases, 1975 (Box 64:, Folder 2569)
  - Salary cases analyzed during Compliance Review, 1972 April (Box 64:, Folder 2570-2571)
  - Task Force recruiting procedures, 1973 Spring (Box 64:, Folder 2572)
  - Title VI (Box 65:, Folder 2573)
  - Title XI (Box 65:, Folder 2574)
  - HEW Federal Regulations and Guidelines, 1972-1975 (Box 65:, Folder 2575)
  - CHE Master Plan, 1974, 1976 update (Box 65:, Folder 2576)
  - CHE Master Plan, 1971-1972 (Box 65:, Folder 2577)
  - CHE Master Plan, 1975 Jul 30 (Box 65:, Folder 2578)
  - Mission Statements (Box 65:, Folder 2579)
  - Master Plan, biennial supplement, 1976 (Box 65:, Folder 2580)
  - Connecticut Master Plan for Vocational and Career Education (Box 65:, Folder 2581)
  - CHE Master Plan (Box 65:, Folder 2582)
  - Resource Group, Reports to CHE (Box 65:, Folder 2583)
  - Master Plan for Higher Education in CT, 1974-1979 (Box 65:, Folder 2584)
  - Study of Educational Programs and Employment Opportunities in Health (Box 65:, Folder 2585)
  - Doctor Orr, Master Plan (Box 65:, Folder 2586)
  - CHE: Colloquium on Higher Education in CT (Box 65:, Folder 2587)
  - CHE: Handbook: Higher Education in CT (Box 65:, Folder 2588)
  - CHE minutes, 1967-1977 (Box 66)
  - CHE Subcommittee on Coordination of Planning (Box 67)
    - Minutes (with attachments), 1966 February - 1977 October
    - Memorandum and Reports, 1966 February - 1977 December
  - SCP Health Professions and Manpower
  - Annual Reports: UConn, 1972
    - Hartford Branch, 1972
    - Southeastern Branch, 1972
    - Stamford Branch, 1972
    - Torrington Branch, 1972
    - Waterbury Branch, 1972
- Series XVI: 2010 Transfers, undated, 2002-2006
  - Academic Ctr./ Institute Review Committee (Box 2010-1)
    - Admissions
    - AAUP
    - Agriculture & Natural Resources
    - Ag. - Vet School
    - Allied Health
    - Alumni Association
    - ANC Partnership
    - Assessment
    - Athletics
    - Athletics
    - Attorney General
    - Avery Point
    - Basketball
    - Board of Trustees
    - Budget Meetings
    - Business
    - Centers
    - CESE
    - Course Fees
    - CPPAC
    - Child Care Implementing Comm.
    - CHIP
    - Chancellor's Comm. - Status of Women
    - CSRA
    - COAA
    - Commencement
    - Continuing Studies
    - CT - Ethics
    - COO/ Linda Flaherty Goldsmith
    - Department of Higher Education
    - Diversity & Equity
    - DHE CEO Meetings
    - Dubai (2 folders)
  - undated (Box 2010-2)
    - E
    - Education
    - Engineering
    - Enrollment Management
    - Events
    - Federal Earmarks
    - Fine Arts
    - Financial Planning & Management
    - Football
    - Fuel Cells
    - Government Relations
    - Global Citizens Task Force
    - Graduate School
    - Hartford Campus
    - Health & Human Development Division
    - Honors Program
    - Human Resources
    - Human Rights Institute
    - IMS
    - International Relations
    - Inge Morath Estate
    - Institutional Research
    - Law School
    - Leave Requests
    - Liberal Arts & Sciences
    - Library Advisory Committee
    - Master Labor Mgmt. Committee
    - Math Reviews
    - Multicultural Affairs
  - undated (Box 2010-3)
    - NASULGC
    - NEASC
    - Norian Estate
    - NSF ERC File
    - Nursing
    - Outreach
    - Pharmacy
    - Phi Kappa Phi
    - President's Office
    - Provost
    - Provost Events
    - Public Health
    - Research & Grad Ed (2 folders)
    - Retirement Committee
    - Roper Center
    - Social Work
    - Stem Cell Initiative
    - Stamford Campus
    - Student Affairs
    - Student Appeals
    - Teachers for a New Era
    - Tech Transfer
    - Textbooks
    - Torrington
    - Tri-Campus
    - UConn Foundation
    - Undergraduate Education
    - UTC Agreement
    - University Senate Meetings
    - Waterbury
    - Women's Center
- Series XVII: Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs [ David Carter], undated, 1964-1983
  - Notes, correspondence, administrative records, clippings, publications, fliers, undated, 1964-1983 (Box 1998-0259-1)
    General note
    Files include the following subjects: Library, New England Board of Higher Education, CHE correspondence
  - , undated, 1964-1983 (Box 1998-0259-2)
    Files include the following subjects: IPC, Amino-Acid Analyzer Service, Changing Degree Auditing, Women's Studies, National Women's Association Convention, Over 62 Educational Programs, A.A.C.C. Policy Advisory Board
- Series XVIII: 2011 Transfer, 1995-2011
  - 1999-2005
    Scope and Contents note
    Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, illustrations, maps, notes, [Subjects include: Building and grounds.]
- Series XIX: Chancellor's Office Records
  - Subseries A: Mark Emmert, 1996-1999 (Box 68)
    Scope and content
    The files were transferred by his assistant after Dr. Emmert left the University. The materials document Dr. Emmert's comments, activities or presence at specific events during his tenure.
    - Alumni Directory statement, 1996
    - Agricultural Faculty retreat, 1996 January 16
    - African-American Cultural Banquet, 1996 April 28
    - Alumni Legislator's Day, 1996 June 26
    - Admissions Video taping, 1996 September 5
    - Agricultural BioTec Groundbreaking, 1996 September 28
    - Admissions Counselor's Day, 1996 October 18
    - Academic Day, 1997 April 14
    - Alumni Community Awards, 1997 April 28
    - Academic Chairs Dinner, 1997 May 23
    - 50th Class Reunion, 1997 June 6
    - Alumni Volunteer Workshop, 1997 September 12
    - American Association for Higher Education, Orlando, FL, 1998 February 1
    - Alumni Teaching and Research Awards, 1998 April 6
    - African-American Cultural Banquet, 1998 May 3
    - Alumni Awards Dinner, 1998 May 29
    - Admissions News Conference, 1998 June 10
    - Academic Department Heads, 1998 August 25
    - Alumni Association Student Scholars, 1999 April 19
    - American Association of University Professors, Excellence and Academic Excellence, 1999 April 28
    - African American Cultural Center Senior Banquet, 1999 May 2
    - Academy of Global Advancement, 1999 May 3